This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates.
Munkini Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy struggled in vain to rescue his brother Ace
from execution at the hands of the Navy.
Marineford was then thrown into chaos by Blackbeard,
who stole Whitebeard's devil fruit power.
Traumatized by the death of his brother,
Luffy is carried away by Jinbei,
who fights to escape the island alongside Whitebeard's surviving crew.
How about I give Marineford a burial at sea?
You can tear down our buildings, but in time we will rebuild them.
But this island is different.
It's more than a symbol of our strength.
It stands in the center of the world.
And that means if we want to protect innocent people from criminals such as yourself,
it must be our stronghold,
so its light can reach every corner.
It doesn't perish, and it will certainly not sink by your hand.
Turn to learn your place.
Well, come on!
Let's see what you're made of!
Destroy them! Destroy them! Destroy them! Destroy them! Destroy them! Destroy them!
Destroy them! Destroy them!
What are these voices in my head?
I dare not base him on dry land, but the sea will aid me!
The water! It's frozen solid!
Amos!
I say, if you're gonna protect someone, then do it right!
I don't like either of you, but if you screw this up, then you'll let the Navy win!
What is that?
It was underwater!
A ship?
It's a submarine!
That's a Jolly Roger!
Quick! Hand over Straw Hat!
Huh? I don't take orders from you, pal!
And besides, what do you want with him anyway, you weirdo?
That's me! Who the hell are you?
Hand him over and we can escape!
He'll die without my help!
What?
Trust me. I'm a doctor.
The Desperate Scream! Courageous moments that will change the future!
Oh, doctor my ass! What kind of doctor carries a giant sword?
And the whole submarine thing is fishy too! What's your deal?
Who is it? Another pirate crew?
It's Trafalgar Law, sir. He's a rookie from the North Blue.
Then he must be Straw Hat's accomplice.
The two started trouble with the Celestial Dragons on Sabahodian while back,
but we weren't able to capture either of them. He's quite dangerous.
They must be planning to escape by submarine!
Stop screwing around! Hand him over!
What's in it for me? What's in it for you?
Captain Law! Navy battleships are approaching from the stern!
Damn it! There's no time! We gotta escape now!
Even if he does survive today,
what makes you think Straw Hat will do you any favors?
He's the son of the most heinous criminal in the world.
He could be your undoing just as easily as he could be your ally.
If you're so determined to stand in the path of justice,
I will grind you beneath its wheels.
Let's finish this and bleed!
Don't let him gain another inch!
That's enough!
You're not laying another finger on Straw Hat or anyone else!
Prepare for combat!
Team A will pursue the Whitebeard pirates
and Team B will stop Blackbeard and his crew at any cause.
The reinforcements are coming from underground!
Do they ever stop?
Finally!
Now let's rush them down!
Hey, pal! You're acting kinda weird!
Snap out of it!
Come on! Let's go!
No, no!
So the leader of the Navy can still slow me down a bit.
Nobody's perfect even with my power.
can still slow me down a bit.
Still, that's not enough.
I'm sinking this dump.
Watch me.
You'll do no such thing.
I'll strike you from this island and from this world.
He stopped the shockwave.
Even the fleet admiral can't faze him.
Hey, Cap, save some for me!
Wee-ha-ha-ha!
What? Hit me!
Gar!
I'm a marine, same as you.
And I've spent enough time feeling sorry for myself.
Ha!
Sorry, Grants!
You're finished!
This is the face of a new era!
Captain!
We're almost within their firing range!
Of course it is, Beppo!
Do something!
Come on!
You just joined the crew and you're already ordering me around?
They've got us surrounded!
All cannons, fire at once!
Sink them!
Fire!
Oh, wait!
You know what?
Not again. Must be Blackbeard doing this. I thought we were done with these earthquakes. This power is a real pain.
Is it just me or is this way stronger than the last time? Watch out, men. This is bad.
This is all wrong. Look at the clouds. Look at this sea. He's staring everything apart.
Come on.
You gotta admit, it's pretty fun to watch.
You didn't forget about me, did you, Cloud?
You forget about us?
What was it?
Block the Marines! Even if we die, our friends can escape!
Don't make me laugh! We're hunting down every last one of you!
Maroon! Another fabulous show, though a bit close for comfort this time.
Yeah, power's not an issue, but control is tricky.
Ha! You're not kidding! If you're gonna sink this place, at least wait till we're not standing on it!
Stop this! It's madness!
Not enough that you killed Whitebeard and Coldblood.
Now you're abusing his power and putting his own crew members at risk with this nonsense!
What? Are you trying to nag me to death? If you got a problem, then do something about it!
I don't play nice! Those days are as dead and gone as Whitebeard!
No one should have that much power! They can't stop him!
It's a nightmare!
No one's safe!
This is a warning from the Saba-Odi Archipelago Emergency Broadcast System.
Following an earthquake at Marineford, a tsunami is expected to hit our southern shores.
Everyone please remain calm and listen carefully for the following safety instructions.
Run for it!
Move it! What are you doing?!
I'm a nobleman! I'll pay good money if you let me go ahead!
Please proceed in an orderly fashion.
Those weird robots are crawling over the crack in the plaza!
Come on! Move! Follow the pacifistas and open fire!
Hey, you okay?
I got this, guys. You two going ahead without me. Are you nuts?!
Look, we have our orders. This makes sense. Better you escape, then all four of us get killed here!
Okay, I guess you're right!
Good luck!
Come on! Stay with me!
What a joke! You're all just marching to your damn graves!
Pops, I'm sorry, but for the first time, I can't follow your orders! I'm gonna fight these guys to the death!
I'm with you. Looks like we'll be joining Pops in Heaven soon enough!
Finally, it stopped shaking.
What the heck is going on with you?
I don't know. There's too much sadness.
What does that mean?
There are all these voices in my head, but I can feel them disappearing one by one.
Huh? Voices?
We'll show you the meaning of justice!
Justice? This is murder!
Hold them off! Let the others escape!
They're criminals! Shoot the bastards in their backs if you have to!
There! That's for my friend, you damn murderer!
You're gonna pay for your crimes and blood, scumback!
We're sending a message, you hear me? We rule this world! Order rules this world!
Got one!
Okay, I know we're all stressed out right now, but you're losing your mind here! Pull it together!
Please, somebody help!
I can't make it! I can't make it!
Ah!
I can't make it!
Kobe!
Hey, wait! Don't run from me!
We're not losing anymore, okay? Now stay back!
We'll save you! You'll be fine! Hear me?
Please, I'm scared.
Leave him. We're not done fighting, dammit.
But, sir...
The pirates are escaping.
Our job is to enforce justice.
We don't have time to tend to the wounded. Go!
Yes, sir.
Kill every last one of them!
Show the world what happens when you defy us!
We've got a man down! Medic!
They're all running away! Just shoot one and move on!
It's not about winning anymore.
They're bloodthirsty. They want revenge!
It went straight through him!
Run!
Chase them down!
Edwin, liar!
Even if our enemies are criminals, this isn't justice.
Their wrongs don't make us right.
They understand.
How's it called?
Noooo!
I...
Nope...
If you're a marine, then follow my lead and strike them down with no mercy!
Kurio!
Yeah! Sakazuki!
Yeah!
Hey, are you alright? Damn it! Get up!
Ha ha ha ha ha! Funny, I don't see anyone stopping me! Or even trying! Are you Navy boys...scared?
Yikes! He's nuts! He's fighting Sengoku now! But I have a feeling, if he gets bored, we'll be next!
Excuse me, friend, but why don't you come on down here?
No, not you!
Kizaru!
Drop them now, you idiot!
You know what, Vaughn? I don't need this right now! I've done enough! They're probably gonna die anyway!
John Vaughn, here they come!
Ooh, nice catch!
Alright, now submerge!
Don't think I forgot about what happened on Saba Odi.
Time to pay!
Whoa! These wounds are pretty bad! Hang in there!
Tam, time to die!
You've done enough!
A marine?
Kobi!
There's no point in fighting anymore! There's no point in killing! It's over! We won! We can end this!
What is he doing?
I can't move!
Please, someone help!
These are human lives! This is wrong!
They have families, children! They're our friends, and we're watching them die!
We killed Ace! Whitebeard is dead! The pirates don't have the will to fight anymore! What are we trying to prove? What's the point? There are wounded men out there! We can save them if we stop fighting! But no, we're just making more victims, more casualties! Those marines have nothing to be proud of!
That's Kobi!
Why are they dying? What are they even fighting for?
Boy, you better run.
You're wasting my time!
Time! If you would impede justice, I have no use for you!
This is it? Not exactly what I'd hoped for, but at least I said what I had to say!
I have no regrets!
Kobi!
A splendid speech touched my heart. And though they were few, those precious moments of courage you showed will change this world. Though only the future will tell if it's for the better, or for the worse.
Inside! I'll be right behind you!
Roger!
I don't think so.
Put your hands up! Now!
Ooh, I'll be Ben Beckman!
Hey, wait a second! I know that ship!
Let's move!
What's he doing here? One of the Four Emperors and his crew!
It's Red-Head Shanks O'Boo!
It's been a long time, old friend.
Let's end this war.
Suddenly, the Red-Hair Pirates appear. As the Navy stares on in shock, Roar tries to escape while suffering heavy fire from the Admirals.
Narrowly missing a reunion with Luffy, Shanks utters a speech on the battlefield that brings the fighting to a halt.
On the next, One Piece, here comes Shanks! The War of the Best is finally over! I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!